Airport.As summer approaches, and due to the effects of the lingering weak yen,
to Japan.One of the problems that arises is the number of
prohibited items carried in suitcases and other items.
Bringing in the
sausage and shredded beef that was in the bag is
prohibited. Meat buns with juicy pork are also prohibited.
Bringing in mangoes, which are in season now, is
prohibited. What are your predictions regarding prohibited items?
is from Canada.
What
will happen if I bring the meat to Japan via transit?And this man, who brought in a large amount of meat, had to
bring it to Japan in an unexpected situation.It
would take a while
because there was a lot of stuff that should not be brought in.  So this time, I decided to find out
what kind of prohibited items are brought into Narita Airport from overseas and why they
are brought into Narita Airport.This
is Animal Rights and Plant Rights, which inspects prohibited items.A woman from Indonesia
is inspected.  What
came out of the cardboard box were
various kinds of food, including fish, fish, fish, etc.It
doesn't matter if the fish is raw or dried.Currently, I'm
bringing in everything,
strange.I ca
n't get into the ferns because they're so big inside, and I'm over there
in Indonesia.  I understand that this is prohibited in Japan.Raw
vegetables
may contain pests that don't live in Japan,
so raw chili peppers from Indonesia
are prohibited.Japan also has them, but they don't taste as good as they do in Japan.
Is that wrong? This is also very spicy.
The book was
supposed to be used for a dish that is not spicy at all. It's extremely
spicy.
However, if you don't give up prohibited items, you won't be able to enter the country.
Next up is a man from Vietnam. Some of the food is
food.  When I flipped
open the inner compartment, I found a large bag
of peanuts.I
opened it and found that it was raw.I could
n't bring it into Japan without it, and I didn't have an illumination book.I didn't have this with me this time, so I could
n't bring raw peanuts into Vietnam.  I
can't bring it in because I don't have an inspection certificate.A male inspector, also from Vietnam,
touches the clothes in the suitcase and notices something strange.When he
takes them out, he sees a round object wrapped in a plastic bag.
Something wrapped in hair came out of my mouth.The things
inside were guava, which is popular in Japan, and
mangosteen, which is called the queen of fruits, a
tropical fruit that is in season right now.In
addition, this is a black genitalia that is not very familiar in Japan.
Are those beans a souvenir? It
's a souvenir for me and my brother, which my father gave to me and my brother from Vietnam.The
results of the test showed that
fruits and vegetables are basically prohibited.
Fruits and vegetables are prohibited from being brought into Japan in order to prevent outsourcing and the introduction of diseases.Next, women
from the Philippines will be
inspected to see if they have items prohibited from being brought in.Open your
bag and
check the contents to see if there are any particular problems.  The inspection was proceeding smoothly,
found some clothes that had been awkwardly placed in them.  Green Island, which is just dried
Green Island, requires a
certificate because it may have been outsourced, which is not available in Japan.Also, it
is prohibited to bring in force from the Philippines.On the other hand, this man from China gets
came out was Chinese azu
and
fresh cherries, which cannot be brought into Japan.I do
n't know, but it's okay to eat them now.It
's no good, so I'm
going to throw them away today.  I'm
n't it prohibited in Japan to bring in cherries?The
small, big, and delicious taste was also
abandoned here.  So
this guy came from fishing in Lanka.When I tried to
look inside the fish, he asked, ``Is it
okay if I take it out?''What's in this?
Well, it's food.What kind of
food is it?I
don't know.  I'm going to take a look at my friend who doesn't
have any. Yes, what came out was a
mysterious package left by a friend who didn't struggle.
Is it okay if I open this? Is it okay? I'll cut a slit
with a cutter and
check the smell.
This is
also this.  Is it a fish? It's a fish.
Well, bring in the fish. O.
What comes out next looks like a fruit. I
open it. I think it's probably a fruit.
Oh, look, I can't bring this in. Ah, it's
something my friend's wife entrusted to me.
Mangoes
and egg trees with a strong sour taste
can peel, so they
cannot be brought into the country, so please be careful not to bring them in.
prohibited.
However, there are strict restrictions in order to prevent pests and plant diseases that occur overseas from
entering Japan.The
same plants are brought in from many packages.Prohibited
had to take a test.I
immediately looked inside her bag
and found it coming out of a paper bag.  I
bought it because I thought it was funny,
but it turned out to be a souvenir that I bought at an airport in China.It was
Snacks And these are sweets that use meat as an ingredient.The
test results indicate that they are meat products,
so you can't bring them with you.But I bought them at a store at the airport.
Yes, in order to prevent livestock diseases that are prevalent overseas from entering Japan,
most products that use meat are prohibited from being brought into Japan, even if they were purchased at an overseas airport.
No, it's meat. Yes, it's no good. Please
tell your fortune here.
Don't worry. All the abandoned meat
brought in a large cardboard box with a large amount of meat inside.  One
of the many sweets
that caught my attention was chichiron, a sweet from the Philippines.Ron
gave me pork rinds made from pork.  It's prohibited to bring in. It
's so delicious
that it's made with pork rinds. You'll want to eat it already. It's
getting stricter each year to bring in meat, so it's important to check before entering the country.
On the other hand, there are some kinds of meat that you can bring into the country.
So this is a couple from France,
this is what the inspector took out of the
food knowyouing me
prod rote ao yeah this chee this cheese
yes yeah cheese o ah that I can speak Japanese
hey hey hey this is canned
hey hey that meat  I can't bring all the food I put in to Japan,
but I can't do this.
Canned
meat is okay. Oh, and canned meat is okay.
But here's the problem:
What country did you buy this from?  Ah,
France. Hmm,
this is no good. I brought it from France.
Inside is
exquisite dish with a rich aroma and sweetness of the meat
. But it's prohibited to bring it in. Even
Next, the
inspection of the woman's bag from the Philippines began, but she was actually
transiting through Japan on her way to Canada. When she
looked inside the bag, she discovered that the fruit
inside was a
mango, which is prohibited from being brought into Japan.  Is it possible to
take the Mago to Canada?The amount of
10.Even if I was transiting overseas, it
was prohibited to bring it into Japan.In the
other than fruits and meat, other foods are also prohibited.  The
man from Mongolia brought in
vegetable seeds and seedlings.The
results of the inspection showed that these seeds,
vegetables, etc.If you don't have this document,
please bring them with you.
Mongolia, unless you apply for it in Mongolia,
collect it, and get an inspection certificate in Mongolia
, you can't bring it into Japan.
Since there is a possibility that you are bringing in canned food, you will also be inspected for animal rights and interests.In
packaging is in Mongolian, so I do
this beef here?I do
n't understand.Do you mind if I open it
?It's a souvenir from a special man.I checked the contents to make sure there were no mistakes.
This is beef, which I didn't write down.I have to declare it for tax.Yes, there is
beef in it.Is this also meat?I ca
n't see what's inside.I wonder if I opened it quite a bit.I
opened it and said, ``Oh,
thank you, yes, inside.''  The meat
in the bowl
is sheep meat, which is a Mongolian favorite.Moreover, you
can find meat one after another.Horse
tongue is popular for its low calorie and rich
taste.  The
meat is delicious, like the tongue.The
meat from the mangoes is
delicious.The meat was brought from Mongolia.It weighed
about 7kg in total.It is
prohibited to bring everything into Japan, and this does
not end with the amount of things that should not be brought to Japan.  There are a lot of
documents, so I have to fill out a lot of paperwork.It
takes a while.Because I
brought in a large amount of meat, I was issued with a
strict warning.If I was found to be
malicious, I could be sentenced to up to three years in prison or
a fine of up to 300,000,000 yen.My wife, who lives in Japan, could be sent to my hometown.
When we looked into the various prohibited items brought in from overseas, we
found that many
people were forced to abandon the items they had brought in because they did not know the rules.  Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much. From the April broadcast, 1 will be
renewed. I will do my best to disappear with all my might.
Check it out and other popular corners will
be even more powerful. Yes, everyone.
Please look forward to Eko's video.
Please be sure to subscribe to my channel.